D.
>> [music]
>> All right, y'all. We are live on this
beautiful Tuesday afternoon. God bless
everybody in the name of Jesus Yeshua
the Messiah. I pray you and your family
are super blessed. I am in a $546,000
Bitcoin long trade plus another 250.
So that that's that's about 750 close to
$800,000 on Bitcoin longs.
All right. We've already locked in
$55,000
US of profit
and we are climbing to the top of the
range to the support resistance flip
where Bitcoin is about to burst
to $74,000.
Now the question is, is that going to
happen? Well, we're getting a a 4hour
red candle of doom printing on the chart
right here. But we're going to discuss
everything that's happening cuz man,
this is some serious business. If you
guys were here yesterday, we were
consolidating around this area. If you
were here yesterday, you saw that we
were in a short trade from this area, a
little bit of a short scalp trade from
that area yesterday. And of course,
guys, if you're in the Casper Crew VIP
Discord where I tell everybody what I'm
doing, right, we took that short trade
yesterday, a little bit of a short
scalperon and cheese. Told everybody my
entry, showed them the position live,
and then I let them know when it was a
good time to hit a TP. We came to the
exact level that we were looking at
yesterday on the stream live, that
$65,000 area at the bottom of the range
where we locked in a little juicy profit
for a scalp trade.
Shout out to the Casper crew where we
gave the long from the 25th of June,
which is currently up right now. Tens of
thousands of dollars from pretty much
the exact bottom. Man, these are some
juicy trades. Are these not juicy
trades? Make sure to smash up the likes,
guys. Make sure to subscribe to the
channel.
Subscribe to the channel. Smash up the
likes
because we're about to give you the
juiciest Bitcoin breakdown here. It's
going to be a really heavy breakdown.
I'm telling you, zero frets will be
pressed except maybe the first fret on
that low drop B flat string on our seven
string guitars [music] ESP LTD Deluxe
through our PV6505s and our 4x12 Mesa
cabs.
Man, look at this. Make sure to smash up
the likes, guys. So, you know what? I'll
be honest with you. All right. When we
zoom out here, we are seeing some very
interesting things on the charts.
[music] Oh my goodness. Did we hit the
PC? Hang on one second.
Okay. Wow. Whoa. Hang on, guys.
Oh no.
I actually didn't realize that we hit
the PC here. This could be it.
Reverse everything I just said. Sell it
all. We've hit the P.
Never fear. Never fear, guys. Never
fear. Okay, let's discuss. I I actually
didn't realize that we hit this PC. So,
we are getting a little bit of a
rejection from a PC. That does change a
few things here. My goodness, that's
actually kind of making me want to FOMO
out a little bit of this of this long
trade here. Maybe I'll I you know what?
I think I actually am going to take a
little bit of profit here.
Yeah, I think I'm going to I think I'm
going to take a little bit of profit
right here. Let's see. Let's see what
how do we do this here?
Oh no. Did I just close the whole trade?
[music]
Oh no, I just closed the whole trade.
>> [music]
[music]
[music and singing]
>> Man,
that's such a bummer. That is such a
real bummer, guys.
That really is such a bummer.
[clears throat]
Oh my goodness. I can't believe I did
that. I I
You know what the problem is? Usually
usually the button on on list mode
when you click close market, it gives
you the option of how much you want to
close. But on detail mode, [music]
it's already preset to close the whole
trade.
So if you market close, you just close
the whole trade.
I see how that works now. [music]
Well, I just closed out a half million
dollar trade by accident.
And honestly,
I'm pretty upset about it. I'm not going
to lie, guys. I'm I'm I'm actually
really upset right now. I know I
shouldn't be. All right. I recognize the
rationality,
but my emotions are very high right now.
I'm not going to lie.
I'm genuinely really upset
cuz I do really think we could see
Bitcoin go to the mid70s
and I was really hoping uh to make that
money, man. I'm not going to lie. Just
be honest, that's a huge bummer. That's
one of those instances where you wish
you could just go and have a quick
doover. You know, I remember when I was
in high school and I broke my humorous.
I broke my humorous doing something
stupid. And you think, man, if I could
just control Z. If I could just have a
few seconds back. Just a few seconds
back.
Oh man.
Oh man. It's the worst. It's the worst.
It really is. It really is. It is the
worst.
Not going to lie. It's It sucks. It
sucks, man. It sucks. So now here I am
holding this stupid short trade. [music]
Supposed to just hedge against my longs.
Oh my goodness. Treadmill stopping now.
All right. Well, you know, big shout out
to everyone in the chat. Big shout out
to Krypto Scarface for the super chat. I
appreciate you, Krypto Scarface.
Oh, man.
Krypto Scarface. God bless you, Jason.
Shout out to you and your community.
Next make or break level is previous
swing high on daily chart 67228.
That is the next make or break level, my
friend.
All right.
Do a giveaway and feel better. You're
right, Senor. You're right. You're
right. We'll do a giveaway. We'll do a
giveaway. We'll do two giveaways.
We'll do two giveaways today. We'll do
our uh we'll do our bitbased $500
giveaway and and I'll also give away
$500 just for the fun of it.
Yeah. Yeah, we'll do two $500 giveaways
today in honor of my [__] move here.
Sheesh, man. Okay. Oh boy.
Yeah, I closed out my short early as
well. I closed out my short from
$126,000
early.
That was a bummer. That was also a
bummer, man. We got a lot of bummers
today. These days, you know, man, I got
to be careful with these dang buttons,
you know. That's that's that people
don't warn you when you get into
trading. Watch out for those buttons.
Those buttons. I'll tell you those
buttons, man. Big shout out to Jesse
Gellick.
Thank you, bro. I appreciate that, man.
God bless you. Thank you for the super
chat. Why not a warning on the platform?
I guess I have the warnings turned off
because you can
order confirmation.
I should have that.
I should have that. It says it's on
here. I'mma hit up I'm going to hit up
Bitbase and say, "Hey, man." Well, you
know, like what the heck? That's what I
thought to myself cuz I looked at it and
I'm, you know, I'm like, "Is this going
to close the whole trade?" I'm like,
"Nah, it'll give me it'll give me an are
you sure?" And then I'll click no.
It didn't give me an Are you sure?
That's actually pretty crazy. That's
actually pretty crazy, man.
[music]
That's actually pretty crazy.
Um, shout out to Barry. [music] Shout
out to Tremble. Do more finger reps.
Shout out to Mole Rock. Mao Rock. I am
shorting. Okay, cool, man. Jason, you
still have your long on Antarctic. Shake
it off. I know. I know. I have a4
million dollar trade on Antarctic,
but I had a half million position from a
super juicy entry,
the last low before the big breakout.
And so now
it's just it's I mean um I mean it's it
is a lot of money that I potentially
didn't make. I mean, if this is the top,
then I made the right decision by
accident, but I don't think this is the
top, guys. I'm just going to be honest
with you. I'm so bullish right now, you
know? I'm so bullish right now. But all
right. Sorry guys.
Got to shake [music] it off. Shake it
off. You know,
you know. Got to shake it off. Sorry
guys.
Oh,
shout out to Mitch La Alistister.
And shout out to Josh for the super
chat. Been watching you since the
Bitconnect days.
Jason Casper didn't even exist back
then,
but I remember those days.
But thank you so much for the super
chat. Josh 99963.
Shout out to Benson Calls who says like
the dang stream. Shout out to Dave
Digital who says like97 is Dave
Digitals. Shout out to Doc the goat.
It's all going to come together like
butt cheeks. [music] Shout out to Patu
X9U.
Shout out to Trencher Top. It happens
sometimes to me, too. Shout out to Sahil
Patel. Hello, sir. Hello to you. Just do
some TA for the next. You'll feel
better. Yeah, man. You're right. Okay,
so let's let's pop right into the chart.
Let's pop right into the chart here.
Okay. Oh, man. We're popping in. We're
popping on into the chart. Oh my
goodness. We're popping on in. Oh. Oh,
man. We're popping on in.
All right. [music] Let's see.
around the blockchain days.
I miss around the blockchain days, you
know. I I I miss Deezy.
I miss Ben Armstrong.
I miss those days. I miss [music] I miss
the last I miss 2020 to 2022. [music]
Those were some good times. 2020 to
2022, those were some good times in
crypto.
Those were some good times in crypto.
Also 2016 to 2018 were some good times
in crypto as well.
But uh yeah, I miss those days, you
know, around the blockchain. Those are
some fun times. [music] You know what
I'm saying? All right, back to the
chart, guys. First of all, we have the
two week confirmed green dot. We talked
about it yesterday. Very rare signal. We
have not seen this since November 2022.
It's pretty crazy. Could this be the
bottom? Well, there is a chance guys
that this could be the bottom, but right
now we are coming up to as many of you
in the chat have mentioned a very key
make it or break it level. Now, let me
just say given the the confirmed bullish
dive on the weekly, I I do think that
Bitcoin definitely has the juice [music]
to come up to the top of our sideways
range and I consider this right here to
be our sideways range. [music] All
right, I do think Bitcoin could come up
towards $80,000 at least toward the
mid70s at the value area high of this
range.
Given the bullishness of everything that
we see happening right now, but what is
happening right now is this. All right,
we are coming up to the PC of this macro
range. This is the range that we've been
trading since February. And here's the
thing. If we flip this into support,
which it looks like we're going to
because when you come up and you wick
into something like this with a quick
wick like that, I I don't think that the
top [music] is in. Obviously, we're
getting a bit of a retrace from here. I
don't think the high is in here. I think
we're going to come up. I think we're
probably going to take the liquidity
from these highs around 673ish
and probably we're going to flip this
thing into support. The reason why I say
that is because
we have a bullish divergence confirmed
on the weekly. [music] We have a bullish
divergence confirmed in the two week.
The money flow is about to cross on the
daily. Now, what would be a gift here in
my opinion given the bullness of these
high time frames. What what I would
really be interested in right now would
be this. All right. If let's say we do
get a a smack hard rejection from here,
right now we're being set up beautifully
for this the shoulder head shoulder
pattern here. [music] when you have a
bullish divergence confirmed and then
you get a money flow cross like this
that next trigger wave if it's a higher
low that's going to be a big move. So
[music] there is a chance that if we do
get a rejection from the top of this
range which very well may happen like
when Asia opens or tomorrow usually the
weekly highs coming in on a Wednesday.
We come up into this area we take the
[music] liquidity we get a rejection
from this PC and we get a harsh move
down. We take all this liquidity here
because remember this this whole channel
has been building downside liquidity.
[music] In fact we have a lot of longs
opening up. If we take a look at the
order flow, let's actually go to the
order flow here. Go to the uno hour time
frame. I mean, look at the longs. Oh my
goodness. We have so many longs opening
up here. We we could easily right now at
least come back down to test 65K.
Uh man, we might we might get a a
significant drop here. [music] But in
general throughout this, let's take a
look here.
We've seen we've seen a a decent number
of longs opening up here. Yeah, it's
nothing too crazy to be honest with you,
but we could definitely grab that
liquidity, stop hunt all these people,
and come back down for the support
resistance flip around the $60,000
level. And that could be that could
actually be the next big opportunity to
take it up to the mid70s. And once we're
up in the mid70s, you know, this is
where we have to wait and see because
again, where we're at in the 4-year
cycle, we are still expecting our low
not to be in until October or November,
right? The fall of 2026 is when [music]
we would expect this low to be in. So
what would be what would be an amazing
scenario in my opinion would be
something like this. We make our higher
low, we get a big pump, and then we just
simply come up to the top of this local
range here [music] and we reject. And
now we come all the way back down. We
make a new low to freak everybody out.
And it happens in the fall, right? And
that's when we actually enter into our
next bull run. Is that the most probable
thing to happen? Here's the thing. I
honestly have no idea. I wish I had more
clarity. Speaking of clarity, the
clarity act. The clarity act. You know
what? Speaking of the clarity act, the
clarity act could be the thing that
actually does give us a big FOMO pump to
the top of the range and then we get a
big reversal, a sell the news event,
which would actually line up pretty dang
nice with an October bottom. All right,
big capitulations, all that kind of
stuff. then we could head into our bull
run. But you know what? I have to say
right now, given the market structure
right now, given everything I see on
market safer right now, I would be
surprised if we don't fill this range to
the to the upside. [music] And I, you
know, I could be wrong on that, but when
you have confirmed twoe divergence,
confirmed weekly divergence, confirmed
daily divergence followed by a money
flow cross, I when was the last time we
had that? [music] When was the last time
we actually had that? You know, and
here's the thing. Do I want to be ultra
bullish right now when the bottom's not
supposed to be in until October? [music]
No, I don't because I want everything to
line up perfectly, right? I want to not
be bullish right now because I want to
say the bottom's not in yet. But things
look objectively bullish, right? The
last time we actually had something like
this, guys, was
bullish divergence and then that first
trigger wave was right around here.
Right around here. Okay. So, like the
last time we had the signal that we're
potentially printing right now where we
got a trigger wave after a bullish
divergence, it was like in the summer of
2025, giving us a pretty significant
move to the upside. The time before that
was right here in September 2024. All
right. So, the last time we printed a
signal similar to what we're printing
right now, where we formed a nice low
and then we came up to the top of the
range and we made a higher low and then
we printed that trigger wave after the
money flow cross. The last time we truly
got the signal that we're potentially
looking to print now for a retrace of
60K was in September 2024. Now, I know
this was facilitated by Trump, but we do
have some potential Clarity Act news
that could trigger a big pump as well. I
don't think it'll be 100%.
But it could set us up very very nicely
for a big pump, a sell the news event,
right? We come down, we get our trigger
wave, big pump, sell the news event, we
get down to our fall bottom, and [music]
then we stay in this range for a little
bit longer, and then eventually by the
time we are in Q12027,
we start to break out. We start to
[music] form higher ranges and stuff
like this. Right? That is kind of what
I'm hoping and looking. Hoping and
looking. Hoping and looking. Hoping and
looking. I can't believe that I closed
that trade, man. Oh my goodness. What
the heck is even wrong with me?
Big shout out to our super chats. Wow.
Shout out to JS Berly 2011. I think
we're going to have to create some type
of defined accumulation. More likely. I
was thinking 687 then back to bottom of
range potentially a spring down to the
40s and up. Exactly. That's exactly what
I'm talking about. And thank you so much
for your super chat. That's exactly what
I'm talking about. Forming some kind of
an accumulation range. Right. So right
here, this would be a mini accumulation
range right down here. Right. We made
our low right here. We took the [music]
low, formed a nice bottom. We come back
up, maybe take the high. We come, we
make a higher low. Then we break out of
this little accumulation range. we come
to the top of our larger range here,
right?
And then, you know, depending on I mean,
you're thinking 68, [music] you know,
I'm thinking maybe 75. Whatever the
case, then we do come down and I would
love a dip into the 40s with a wick and
then we come back up and we continue in
this range here before eventually
breaking out. Like, this is what I hope
for. This is really what I hope for.
This would just be so perfect in every
possible way, you [music] know. Um,
this would be so perfect in every
possible way right here uh for our fall
bottom, right? Our our [music]
September, October, November bottom
where we're where it's this big kind of
choppy range,
[music] chopping people up left and
right, left and right, up and down.
You know, Bitcoin price doesn't make a
sound. We're chopping them left. We're
chopping them right, chopping them up,
chopping them down. But the Bitcoin
price don't make a sound. Jay Casper on
the treadmill. What a clown.
Now we are in this 4hour time frame here
getting a little bit of a rejection from
the PC. And if we do print a red dot on
the 4 hour, I do just want to point out
the fact guys
that this very well. Actually,
I don't I I'll be honest with you. Do I
think that I think we're going to go for
the highs? I think we're going to come
up toward the $68,000 level here. But
this this money flow dib on the 4 hour
could I mean I didn't realize we hit
this PC. I thought the PC was a little
higher. Um but we do have some
divergence forming here. This this could
turn into something. This could turn
into some downward action. This could in
a perfect world now that I accidentally
closed out of my half million long
trade. In a perfect world, this could
take us down to $60,000
where I would love to uh long that. Is
that really going to happen? Well,
probably not because I because I because
I'm hoping it does. Let's Let's pull
some other Let's take a look at this
whole uh range here. I want to look at
the volume from the low.
[music] Uh let's look at the just the
volume of this channel here.
All right, let's look at the volume more
of this range here.
Yeah, that's some nice confluence down
at these lows. I have to be honest. Like
right now, like if I had to choose a
long trade for me, it would have to be
this. It would have to be this.
This would have to be my trade of choice
right now for a long trade. As for a
short trade, what would my trade of
choice be? My trade of choice right now
for a short trade would have to be this,
guys. Because we're seeing such bearish
money flow here [music] on the 4 hour.
It would be really nice if we just did
something like this
and got one more high and got now a
local div here on the 4 hour and just
more bearish div on the 1 hour. That
would that would actually be my short
trade of choice. My short trade of
choice right now would be this
a little bit higher
and then take it down to around 60K.
And then my long trade of choice right
now would be [music] coming down to 60K
and then taking it up uh to the uh
[music] to the value area high of this
range. So this this pretty much I'd say
the two main opportunities I'm
interested in right now, right? I'm I'm
also curious. Let's let's pull some
other things here on the chart.
Um let's pull some other things on
chart. Let's pull an anchored VWAP from
the low.
This anchored VWOP has actually been
acting as support, too. So, keep your
eyes on this anchored VWOP. It might act
as support again if we're if because if
we don't come down to 60K and we just
continue to trade in this Chop City
channel here,
maybe we simply just come down once
again to this
this anchored VWOP. Let's pull the
anchored VWOP actually also from the top
and let's see
let's see where that actually comes in.
Wow. Yeah. I mean, this this lines up
very beautifully with the short idea.
Yeah. So, I'm definitely interested in a
short from here, guys. We're seeing the
medium time frame divergences really
start to form.
Um,
big shout out to Crypto Scarface. Even
if Bitcoin breaks market structure
bullishly, it's allowed to test lower
levels, including 60K, and remain in a
bullish structure. Absolutely. Yeah.
Just because we're flipping uh $67,000
doesn't mean we're not going to come
down to 60. Yeah, it would just be in my
opinion if we do come up to this area
and get a rejection.
I would expect a retra retrace and I
would be looking to long to dip because
in this case, right, if we do come up to
let's say 6768K,
now we're making a higher high here,
right? We're making a higher high and
that is our first sign of a reversal.
And so then we would look for a higher
low, right? We'd look for that higher
low and that would again that would give
us our head, our shoulder, our head. Do
you ever see a person that has two heads
and one shoulder in the middle? It's a
very strange sight. All right, they have
two faces on the on the deltoids
and then they have one shoulder in the
middle. All right, it's a very strange
site, but it it does exist, so they say.
All right, shout out to the super chats.
Shout out to the regular chats. Um
DBK Wahoo says [music] the lunar
eclipsees marked the near top all-time
high and will mark the near bottom just
the same. It has it has in all prior
cycles. Interesting.
I didn't know that about the lunar
eclipses.
eclipses. Do I like to dance date
digital? Uh no actually I don't like to
dance at all. Clarity Act passing might
create the same effect as when the Black
Rockck ETF was introduced. Exactly. The
first thing actually that happened when
the ETF was introduced, my friend, is
actually we pumped.
And that's what I'm hoping happens. I'm
hoping here's what I hope happens. All
right, let's clean up this chart a
little bit. Um [music] I am hoping that
this Clarity Act or whatever the case,
whatever it's called,
>> I'm hoping it does what what it did like
just like when the ETF was launched. Do
you guys remember when the ETF was
launched? We didn't nuke right away. No,
we we pumped. We pumped. Here is the ETF
being launched. Happened right here.
All right. And we got a move up of about
11%.
Before the nuke.
And this is exactly what I hope happens
with the Clarity Act, right? I'm hoping
the bullish news can push us up to some
of these resistances and then we make a
lower low and then we pump. That's
exactly what I am hoping happens. Now,
this was a very key resistance. If you
guys remember, that was a beautiful easy
short trade.
That was a beautiful easy short trade.
We shorted that during the Casper Crew
uh New York Open live stream. [music]
And the reason we shorted was because we
just tapped into the 618. It was such an
easy trade. I'll never forget. I said,
"If we lose the 618, I'm short." Then we
shorted it live in the VIP live stream
and um that was a beautiful trade by the
way. Now I was expecting a little bit
lower but that's what I hope happens
now. Like I hope right now the clarity
act like if we do like come up here come
back down to 60k and then I you know the
clarity act could give us a pump up to
the mid70s and then sell the news right
the rumor sell the news kind of thing.
That's kind of what I hope would happen.
That would be pretty cool. And you know
what?
Yeah. I mean, that's that that's pretty
pretty awesome idea right here. You know
what? When it comes to planning for
trades, I would say what I hope happens
what I hope happens is this.
>> [music]
>> I hope that we can grab a short from
here,
come down to back test this support,
grab a long trade from here,
pump it up to
the Clarity Act golden pocket, and then
short it down to a new low. This would
be my ideal trading plan right now.
Like,
if I was a trader, if I was a Bitcoin
trader,
this is what I would like. This is what
I would like here. [music] What a
beautiful a beautiful uh trap for
traders of all sorts. But what a what a
wonderful opportunity this could be. You
know what I'm saying? This could be an
really nice opportunity. Um [music]
red dot in the 4 hour. Let's check it
out. Let's check out our 4 hour red dot
market cipher B.
Yeah, it's not confirmed yet, guys.
Right. It's not confirmed yet. We still
have two hours for this dot to confirm.
If this dot does confirm,
again, so far, like, let's just be
honest here. So far, these red dots and
these bearish divergences, these
extremely bearish diverges, and let's
not forget, you know, in the Casper
crew,
we shorted this thing here, right, in
the VIP Discord. And it looks so
bearish. So bearish, but we still made a
higher low. So don't be surprised, guys,
if we continue to make higher lows here.
That that is one possibility.
Possibility number one with this 4hour
red dot is we just continue to hold this
anchored VWAP here. It has been support
the whole time. In fact, I'm going to
add an alert on this anchored VWOP
in case in case just in case you know I
need to FOMO into a long trade now that
I accidentally close out my long trade.
Oh. Oh my goodness.
Ah,
I hope we I hope we make a lower low
here, man. But man, this is this is some
serious.
[music]
What a what a bummer, man. I'm not going
to lie. What a bummer, man. What a
bummer. What a bummer. What a bummer. I
can't believe I did that, man. I can't
believe I actually did that. That sucks
so bad.
Can you guys believe I did that?
I can't believe I did that.
I can't believe I did that,
>> you know.
Wow. Wow.
Wow.
It's like the time I found out my wife
was pregnant. Wow. I can't believe I did
that.
Pregnant? How did that happen? You know,
if only I could take those 2 minutes and
35 seconds back
pregnant. [music]
But how?
Close the trade. But how did I do that?
Pulled the trigger too early. Pulled the
trigger too early. In both situations,
got to be careful. You got to really
control the trigger, fellas. Fellas, let
me give you a little life advice here.
All right.
You got to control the timing when it
[music] comes to clicking that close
trade button. Remember on Bitbase, okay,
on Bitbase,
if it's on details mode, if you click
market close, it will close the trade
without warning the whole thing unless
you come here and upper or lower the
amount.
Oh my goodness. I can't believe I did
that. I can't believe I did that. What
did I do, Kirk Patrick? I closed a
$575,000
position that was long.
All right. From the from this low here,
I closed out a position completely by
accident because I wanted to take some
profit out. Just a little profit. I
wanted to take a little profit out.
Instead, I closed the whole trade, which
is is not good [music] because I I do
think we're going to eventually probably
flip this into
into support here. Right? So, I I I made
a big mistake. [music] You can go back
and watch it live. All right. That's
what's happened here.
[music] You know, that's what's happened
here.
[music]
Sheesh.
Are we losing VWAP now? All right, let's
take a look. Let's take a look. [music]
Let's take a look.
I can always open another trade from the
bottom. Yeah. Yeah, I know. But here's
the thing. Like, am I going to have that
opportunity?
I don't know.
I don't know,
man. It's about to get so serious,
though.
I don't know.
Hey yo, I don't know. Jay [music] Casper
so furious. Closing all the trades cuz
your boy is delirious. I closed it early
and now I'm [music] so furious. So sit
back. You know you want to hear this. J
Casper in the house shorting [music]
Bitcoin from the top. No bounce. About
to dump it back down to the bottom.
Bitcoin about to crash. Can you spot
them? Cuz the candles turning [music]
purple then they turning blue. Cuz the
Bitcoin price about to show you what she
going to do. Just sit back, relax. I'll
take you to the trading school. Jason
Cer walking every day. Your boy is not a
fool. We got the family jewels. [music]
The J Casper crew
cuz you know we're [music] not fools. We
can fix it cuz we got the tools. Yeah.
The candle turning red. Jake Casper on
the treadmill. Got the bars in his head.
Can't believe [music] that my live trade
ended up dead. Close it early. 50 Kevin
7K ahead [music] 10. H I can't be mad
about the profit. A pretty big number,
baby. Can you spot it? But my mind is
full of all the whatifs. If the Bitcoin
[music] doesn't fall down the cliff, I
thought, "Oh my goodness, about to pump
to 74." Imagine the money I could have
made through the door. If we came up to
here like before, my mouth [music] would
be down to the floor cuz we'd be up 100K
in the profit. Can't believe it. Can you
spot it? It [music] wasn't meant to be.
I close the trade early. Eating cheese
like my name is Shirley.
Shirley [music] Temple. She's the one I
look for with a rental. Go to
Blockbuster to rent the VHS. J [music]
Cra, you know he does it best. In the
gym, only train arms and chest. Only
skip leg day cuz that is the best. Yeah.
[music] And we're curling in the squat
rack. Can I work in? Heck no. Never come
back.
We got [music] 10 sets of 20 barbell
curls in the squat rack. Not funny. We
got to get [music] the pump. Get the
bicep veins. Jay Casper on the trains.
Your boy is insane. Ah, cuz it's up in
the membrane. Inside, [music] outside.
It's about to rain. The sky is so dang
cloudy. The Bitcoin price is getting
rowdy.
[music] That beat is so serious. I just
can't help myself. I just can't help
myself when that beat comes on. I'm
sorry, guys. Uh,
big shout out to LA Apologetics in the
house. What's going on, bro? It's good
to see you, man. It's good to see you
here, bro. I didn't know you parttook in
the crypto leverage trading uh content
here.
Um,
yeah.
[music] Let's see.
All right. Here's the thing, guys. We
are going to give We're giving away
$500.
We're giving away $500 today. We're
going to be giving away Shout out to
Buen. We have to take a look at VWOP
first of all.
Are [music] we losing the VWAPator?
Let's Let's put on the VWOPator.
The picture of [music] Buen reminded me
of the VWOP.
Let's see.
We're we're we're trying to hold the
VWAP. If we lose this VWOP, we're we're
we're coming down. All right. Maybe I
maybe I did make the right move by
[music] closing that dang trade. But
sheesh, I I'm
giving away $500 courtesy of Bitbase.
But also because I closed a trade early,
I'm also going to give away $500.
I'm going [music] to give away $500. So,
you know what? For the Bitbase giveaway,
you guys need to have a user ID signed
up with my Bitbase affiliate link. For
the $500 giveaway, you don't have to do
anything because I'm going to send that
to you right from my own personal crypto
wallet.
All right. My PCW.
My PCW right to you. PCW right to you.
You know it's true.
So, let's do a $500 giveaway now. All
right.
Let's do a $500 giveaway right now.
Um,
what I need you guys to do is spam the
chat with your USDT address. All right.
Spam the chat with your USDT address.
>> [music]
>> And then I'm going to count down from
10.
And uh whoever gets whoever [music] gets
uh whoever's USDT address gets uh
checked first wins. All right. So spam
the chat with your tether address. All
right.
Your PCW is a Glock. [music]
Spam the chat with your Tether address,
guys.
And we'll do a screenshot. Whoever gets
captured in the screenshot will win
$500. Maybe we'll do multiple $500
trade. I mean, sometimes when I'm in a
bad mood, I just give away hundreds of
or thousands of dollars. Honestly, why
not? Maybe we'll do four, five, six,
$500 giveaways. I don't know. I don't
know. I can't see the future.
Apparently, if I could, I wouldn't have
closed that trade early. [music] All
right. All right. Let's count down and
see who our winner is. 10 9 8 7 6
C sinko quattro trace do uno boom all
right let's see who the winner is it is
officially
uh cakes case [music]
6448.
All right 6648. All right I got your
address right here.
>> [music]
>> I'm going to send it to myself.
[music]
Send it to myself.
All right.
All right. Send it to myself. All right.
Send it to myself. All right. All right.
Send it to myself. And now I'm going to
send you $500 from my PCW.
My personal crypto wallet. Jay Casper
about to send it from the PCW.
Man, I can't wait to eat a high calorie
meal, man. I cannot wait to eat a super
high calorie meal.
>> I'm going to eat a high calorie meal. I
already had a high calorie. Ah, it
wasn't that high. 1,500 calories for
breakfast.
Probably going to eat over 5,000
calories today. [music]
Let's see.
Let's see here.
All right.
Congratulations for winning the money.
Let's [music] see.
We're going to go ahead and send you
that $500 right now.
Looks like a an Ethereum address.
[music]
[music] Looks like an Ethereum address
in AD201. Haz 2011.
[music]
Yep. Yep. Yep. All right.
All right. Look at that. Look at that.
[music] We just sent it.
500 USDT, baby. Straight to you. [music]
Straight to your address.
All right. Congratulations.
Should we do another giveaway?
Should we give it Should we Maybe we
will in a little bit. We're still going
to do the Bitbase giveaway. Okay.
[music]
We're still going to do the Bitbase
giveaway today.
The Bitbase giveaway. You closed your
short by accident. [music] Dang, man.
What is What is going on today with
those traders closing all these trades
by accident? Seriously, what is going
on?
You know what? You know what sucks? You
know what sucks? I'll tell you guys what
sucks. I'll show you what sucks. I'm
going to show it to you guys. All right.
When I go onto my dang Bitbase mobile
app,
it has that 2 seconds of refresh.
You know, the two seconds of refresh.
You know what I mean? So, for a second,
for a split second,
I saw my open long trade. Oh. Oh.
Just to tease me. Bit babe. Why you got
to do that?
H. You guys know. Don't you hate the
dang the dang when the when the when
when the when the uh when the uh when
the when the um you know
when the app refreshes, you know what I
mean, guys? You guys know what I mean,
right? You log into your trading app and
it takes a few seconds to update
everything, [music]
you know?
It still shows your open position
even [music] though it's closed out. Or
worse, you long what you thought was the
bottom. You go to [music] sleep
overnight. You get wicked out and then
in the morning price pumps. You open up
the app and you're up for like a split
second. You're like, "Whoa, awesome."
And then trade is closed. They're like,
I feel like they do that on purpose,
just to spike the dopamine cuz they want
us to come over here and click uh
however much money 3,637
$3,637,000
and just click long. It's not even going
to give me the option to say, "Are you
sure?" They want the dopamine hit. We're
going back up, baby. Should I click long
now? $3,600 position, 20x leverage. What
could happen? What could go wrong? What
could possibly go wrong? Buy the dip,
they said. Buy the dip. What do you call
this? It's a dip. Buy the dip, they
said. Just buy it. What could happen?
What could go wrong?
Relax, Jason. I always keep this bug
zapper here in case I get too bullish. I
just push the button and zap my dick.
Ah,
it does hurt. It actually hurts quite a
bit.
We are going to still have to do a bit
base giveaway.
Preparing for miss the giveaway. Um,
I'm sorry. Uh, preparing for, but we are
going to do another giveaway. Um, we're
going to do the Bitbase giveaway.
It's a big amount. What? $500 is a big
amount.
$500 is a big amount in Africa. Well,
we're going to we're going to do another
giveaway.
Um, [music]
market makers told Bitbase to close J
positions and then we'll pump. Man, that
would suck, honestly. Um, they meant buy
the sour cream and onion dip. See,
that's the thing. They meant buy the
sour cream and onion dip. Yeah. [music]
Yeah, buy the sour cream and onion dip.
All right, guys. Let's do a Bitbased
giveaway, then maybe we'll do another
giveaway. All right, so Bitbase, guys,
you have to have a user ID using the
affiliate link in the description of
this video.
So, go ahead and spam the chat with your
user ID.
All right. And we'll do a bit based $500
giveaway and then I'll just do another
$500 giveaway myself this stream, guys.
I'm I'm just in the mood to give away
money. You guys ever get in the mood to
give away money?
I get in that mood sometimes. You know
what I'm saying?
Is this a What is this? [music]
Yeah. Spam your user ID for Bit Base.
We'll do that giveaway and then we'll do
another $500 giveaway from my own
personal crypto wallet. My PCW,
my good old PCW, you know,
you know.
All right.
All right. Here we go. 10 9 8 [music] 7
6 5 4 3 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 [music] 3 10 9 8
10 9 8 7 6 5 a four a three. I said 10 a
9 8 7 6 [music]
5 5 4 to the 3
J. You know, we're about to click the
button and we're gonna [music] do a
giveaway cuz we lost money cuz we closed
a trade. But we're about to do the
giveaway anyway. Big shout out to Bit
Base all up in the face trading crypto
all over the place. You got a mobile
[singing] phone and some nice Wi-Fi. You
could trade crypto while you're on the
fly. I said 10 98 765 4. Wait. Uh 10
[music] 98 765 43. Better wait. Start
again. I said 10. Chicka
[music and singing] chicka slim shady 78
654 and we're GG unit through the gate,
baby. Oh yeah. Look at Jay Casper. He's
about to click the button even faster.
Boom. All right, we [music] got a
screenshot. Let's see who the winner is.
We're preparing for war. Oh no. [music]
Prepare for bro. Bro, wrong post, man.
>> [laughter]
>> It's the wrong thing, man. It's not
supposed to be your address, bro. It's
supposed to be your your user ID. Oh,
no.
All right, we're going to have to do
another We're Dang. We're going to have
to do another preparing for war. I'm
sorry. This is the bit basic way. We
need the user ID, man. Not the uh All
right, here we go. Let's do it. Let's do
it. User ID. Spam the user IDs. All
right. 10 9 8 7 6 4 3 2 1. Boom. All
right. Let's see who the winner is now.
Now the winner is
Iggyan. Iggyan. Congratulations Iggyan.
Iggyan.
All right Iggy son.
Shout out to Iggy son.
[snorts]
I'm actually going to hit up your base
now and say
that I closed trade by action. We should
fix that.
All
right, Iggyan, congratulations.
[music] Iggy son,
congratul.
[sighs]
All right, cool. Well, yeah. You know, I
feel I feel like we should do another
$500 giveaway, you know?
Should we do another $500 giveaway? If
you think we should do another $500
giveaway, spam the chat as much as you
can and like the video. How many likes
do we have? We have 200 li. Let's get up
to 400 likes. 400 likes
and we'll do the 500 giveaway. And like
literally, we just need a third of the
people in here to like the dang stream.
and we'll do a $500 giveaway. All right,
let's do it. Pump up the likes, baby.
Look, it's tough out here for us crypto
YouTubers, man. No one's into crypto
right now. You know, views are down.
Views are down.
You know,
the hype is over. Yeah, people want the
giveaway. All right, people want that
giveaway. All right, people want they
want the giveaway. People want the
giveaway. It's understandable.
It's understandable.
Wow.
All right, we're going to get it. We're
going to get the likes. Don't worry.
We're holding the VWOP for now, guys.
All right, you see that? We're holding
the VWOP. Maybe we get a little bounce
from the VWOP.
Man, I I'm I can't believe I closed that
trade, man. That really does suck. I've
been so I've been swing trading so well
lately. And that was that was a juicy
one. That was a Oh goodness.
Alrighty.
Shout out to everybody in the chat right
now, guys. Um,
yeah. Shouts to everybody in the chat.
I have no account, but like the video.
Well, look, you don't need an account
for my $500 giveaway. This is not coming
from an exchange. This is coming from
yours truly. All right. This is coming
straight from my PCW. My personal crypto
wallet. Okay?
Straight from my personal crypto wallet.
my PCW,
you know,
man, I cannot believe I closed that
trade. Like, what the heck?
[sighs] Oh, man. I hope we come back
down to 60K, guys. It's not going to
happen because I closed the trade.
That's just how life works, right?
It's just how it works.
It's just how it works. But whatever,
man. Whatever.
We'll get the next one. I'll get the
next one. I'll get the next one.
Shout out to man Meta416.
Shout out to make me a millie. He says
no need to spam guys unless asked.
What address does he want? USDT Mo
trades. Mo trades. I'm not giving away
no BTC. I'm just giving away USDT.
You know, $500 USDT. Look, we're giving
away $1,500 today.
$1,500 giveaway.
>> That's That's That's awesome. That's
crazy.
Look, on this channel, we pay you to
stay. You know, most YouTubers, man,
they're stingy, right? They don't want
to pay you to stay. Look, I'mma pay you
to stay. I'mma pay you to stick around.
You know, like the video. I'll pay you
$500. Please. Please. Just like the
video, please.
Oh, no. with Splash Films missed MU by
an inch and now it's up 20%. Yeah, it
happens, man. It's just one of them
days. It's one of those days, you know.
It is one of those days.
Oh my goodness, man. It is one of those
days. Way to turn. [music] What? What?
What? What? I mean, look, I I'm sorry.
I'm not going to speak any more of this
matter.
All right.
I will speak no more of this matter.
Would
I take profit on my long hair?
I said I will speak no more of on this
matter.
You know,
all these wallet addresses. It's cuz I'm
giving away $500, Tom. And the way I do
it is people spam their wallet address,
but they shouldn't do it until I tell
them to do it first. We need to get
another like 100 likes. We need to get
another 50 likes. Just another 50 likes.
And then we'll do it, right?
Then we'll do a $500 giveaway.
The likes are pumping, baby. The likes
are pumping right now.
Oh, shout out to make me a millie. He's
going to time out people who are posting
their address and not being patient.
Yeah, that's good, man. That's good. I
think you should. Yeah, I think you
should do that.
Yeah, I think you should do that.
And
we're super close. We just need like 20
more likes, guys. 20 more likes. Smash
them up. Smash them up. Smash them up.
Smash them up. Smash them up. Smash them
up. Smash them up.
up. Smash them up. Smash them up. Smash
them up. Smash them up. Smash [music]
them up. Smash them up. Smash them up.
Smash them up. Yeah. Smash them up.
Smash them up. Smash them up. Smash them
up. Smash them up. I [music] said smash
them up. Smash them up. Smash them up.
Smash them up. Smash them up. Oh yeah.
384 likes. Got to [music] smash them up.
We're hyper from the coffee in the cup.
We got the caffeine flowing through my
veins. It's getting me a bit insane in
the membrane. [music]
All I want to do is see some change. But
sadly, things always stay the same. Cuz
you know I'm taking trades [singing]
just to make the change. So serious I
never play. Uh hit it [music] up. Pump
it up. Pump them up. Uh smash the like.
Smash the like. Smash the like. Yeah.
Smash [music] the like. Smash the like.
Smash the like. Yeah.
[music] Smash the like. Smash the like.
Smash the like. Yeah. All right. We got
the likes. Now you can spam the chat.
Now you can spam the chat.
All right.
All right. Now you can spam the dang
chat. All right. Here we go.
[clears throat]
We're going to count down from 10
and whoever's wallet address is
highlighted
wins $500.
500 USDT.
All right. 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1. All
right. Let's see who the winner is. The
winner is Xander 6204.
Wait, Xander 6204. Where is Xander?
Xander. Xander. Xander. Xander. Oh crap.
Xander.
All right. Xander.
All right. If I can't find Xander, I'm
going to [music] have to copy the
address manually. I'll have to copy the
address manually.
[music]
Yeah, I think I'm going have to do it.
Yeah, I'll have to do it.
>> [music]
>> Yeah, I'll have to do it. I'll have to
copy the address manually. It's all
good. It's all [music] good. It's all
good. All right. Shout out to Xander
6204.
You know what I'm going to do?
You know what I'm going to do? I'll tell
you. I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
I'm going to use
Chad GBT
copy address so I don't make a dang
mistake. All right.
Congratulations to Xander
6204.
Congratulations,
[music]
Xander 6204, for winning $500.
Shout out to Key
for our first win
and Iglissan for our second win [music]
and Xander 6204
for our third win.
Congrats guys. Congrats. Congrats
to all winners.
All right, let me just verify this
address here.
>> [music]
>> All right.
All right. Cool, man. About to send you
the money right now. All right.
Man, I can't believe what happened. The
matter I will speak no more of, but
sheesh, I can't believe that happened.
You guys believe that happened? I cannot
believe that happened,
man. I can't believe that happened. What
a crazy day. It is a crazy day.
All right.
Big shout to our winner.
All right. There's the address.
There's the amount.
All right. Congratulations
[music]
preparing uh uh LA apologetics says come
to Yeshua too and you will always be a
winner. Amen. Amen. That's the truth,
right?
Um.
All right.
All right, guys. You know, I think I'm
going to call it a stream. All right.
I'm going to call it a stream today.
It's been one of those days, man.
Hopefully, Lord willing, tomorrow we
come back. Casper Crew VIP stream.
playing for a juicy long trade and long
to bottom and short to top cuz the
Casper crew baby just don't stop. All
right, God bless y'all. Peace.